== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
(Penny:)Okay, so it's not
a legal ceremony,
(Penny:)it's just a chance for us
(Penny:)to redo our vows
so everyone can be part of it.
So there's no maid of honor?
(Penny:)No.
(Amy:)Huh.
(Amy:)But if I were to, say,
wear a purple satin dress
(Amy:)with a sweetheart neckline
and stand near you,
(Amy:)you wouldn't be able
to stop me, right?
(Penny:)I don't see how I could.
(chuckles)
(Amy:)Then I graciously accept.
(Bernadette:)Who's going to officiate?
(Penny:)I was kind of hoping you would.
(Amy:)Wait, now I'm just some
lousy maid of honor?
(Sheldon:)Hey, good news, I just got off
the phone with my mother.
(Sheldon:)She is coming to the wedding.
(Penny:)Okay, wait,
(Penny:)you're inviting people
to our wedding?
(Sheldon:)Yes, I'm inviting
people to our wedding.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, I've already asked
(Sheldon:)Stephen Hawking
and Robert Downey Jr.
(Sheldon:)And now, don't get your hopes
up, 'cause he's pretty busy,
(Sheldon:)but Erno Rubik.
(Bernadette:)Who's Erno Rubik?